bottlestore.com 2019-02-04

# Bottlestore.com Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting your privacy! This policy provides you with details on the information we collect from you and the uses we make of your personal information. If you have any questions, please email us at [sales@bottlestore.com](mailto:sales@bottlestore.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy). Each time you visit www.bottlestore.com (“Website”), through the use of cookies our Web server automatically recognizes your domain name and email address (where possible). You have the option of disabling cookies by accessing the tools provided to you in your Internet options. However, please note that you may not have full access to the Website if you change your cookie settings to disable them.

This policy may be updated from time to time without prior notice, so please check back periodically. If you continue to visit this Website and use the services made available to you after such changes have been made, you hereby provide your consent to the changes.

BottleStore is the sole owner of the information collected on www.bottlestore.com. BottleStore collects information from our users at several different points on our Website.

We encourage you to read this policy to learn more about:

  1. What information of yours is collected by this Website.
  2. How you can opt-out of receiving communications from us.
  3. The security of your information.
  4. Links to other Websites made available to you by this Website.
  5. Product Reviews
  6. How to contact us with any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy

  1. ## Information Collected

    1. ### Personally Identifiable Information

If you join our e-list a user is required to give their contact information (such as name, address and email address). We use this information to send the customer marketing emails. It is optional for the user to provide unique identifiers (such as, username and password), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience. When an order is placed with us, you may be asked to provide your name, address or credit card information in connection with your use of the Website (including without limitation, by your submission of purchase orders.) This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer orders.

    2. ### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Certain non-personally identifiable information about our visitors is collected by the standard operation of our Internet servers and through the use of cookies (small amounts of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with the Website technology, such as the type of Internet browser you are using and the domain name of your internet service provider, where you go within the Website and how much time you spend in any particular area, search queries, impressions and other data). The information we collect is (1) used to improve the content of our Website and enhance your experience, and (2) for us to contact our customers. All information that is collected is on an 'opt-in' basis and users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' at any time.

    3. ### Third Party Cookies

BottleStore has engaged a third party service provider, to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to the Website to help us administer our Website in order to constantly improve the Website quality. We do track and analyze personally identifiable usage for customers who have completed a purchase or signed up for our e-list. The provider uses cookies to help track visitor behavior and BottleStore sets cookies. It does not use cookies to relate Website visitors to any personally identifiable information and provides BottleStore with information about site usage that reflects individual behavior of visitors, but not their identity. All data collected by the provider on behalf of BottleStore is used only to provide us with information on site usage and is not shared with any other third parties.

  2. ## Opt Out

Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe or remove in the subject line in the email or email us at sales@bottlestore.com. In addition to this, all email correspondence that we send you will include a link which when accessed by you, will enable you to remove yourself from our mailing lists. Please note that there might be a brief delay between when you submit your request to opt-out and when it is processed and reflected in our systems; accordingly you might continue to receive communications from us for a limited time after you unsubscribe.

  3. ## Security

We are committed to using our best efforts to maintaining the security of your Personal Information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we adhere to industry standard practices and procedures to help safeguard and secure the information we collect. Although we use our best efforts to protect the security of your Personal Information and our system, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, no transmission via the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of this and other factors beyond our control, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you transmit to or through our Website. Therefore, you assume that risk by using the Website.

  4. ## Links

This Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, BottleStore, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

  5. ## Product Reviews

We may provide areas on our Website where you can post reviews of products. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use. In addition, such postings may appear on other Websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Once you have posted information, you will not be able to edit or delete such information.

  6. ## Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
Phone: 908.851.2659  
Email: [sales@bottlestore.com](mailto:sales@bottlestore.com?subject=%27Privacy%20Policy%27)  
Postal Address: 3 Milltown Court, Union NJ 07083  
Website URL: www.bottlestore.com
